Let's do it. What's up, brother?
How are you? I'm great. Oh, I should
have brought my pen.
We actually have CJ's rookie contract
from 2016 with that this would be fun
for you to have. 5'9 2016 That's crazy.
I've been saying I got two questions.
Um
can we negotiate a signing bonus right
now?
Got that covered. My man. Thank you.
And does this add another year to my to
my insurance benefits?
>> [laughter]
>> Remember when you walked in the door,
you know, as as as a young tryout player
and then you grew into
the leader of our team, the rock of our
locker room.
Look at that. We just appreciate
everything you've done for your career
and you know
you're always a part of this Vikings
family.
>> I appreciate it. I got to go spend this
signing bonus money.
Come on. You want it?
You got it.
Thank you.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you, guys.